SIMPLY DAS

REGISTERED ARCHITECT COUNCIL OF ARCHITECTURE

Having professional experience in the field of Architecture, Planning and Interior Design worked on various scale of projects of diverse in nature & region ranging from Premium Residential Complexes, Condominiums, Luxury Villas as well as Boutique hotels was also responsible for preparing Architectural Design, Plans, Rendering the 3d visualizations, Working Drawing & Detail Drawings.

Believes in dedication, wants to explore the diverse sector of the field to gain a strong aptitude for detailing, to gainexpertise in site services and to achieve team organization skills to handle complex project in a holistic approach.

Experience

2021/2- Present	Locus(Bengaluru) Junior Architect
2019/11- 2020/12	Maheshwari & Associates Junior Architect
2017/06- 2017/11	Raj Agarwal & Associates Intern Architect

Education

2013/08- 2018/05	Piloo Mody College of Architecture Biju Pattanaik University of Technology Bachelor of Architecture
2011/07- 2013/05	Kendriya Vidyalaya,Garden Reach Central Board of Secondary Education, Delhi AISSCE
2002/04- 2011/05	D.A.V Public School, Kolkata Central Board of Secondary Education, Delhi AISSE

Personal Info

Permanent Address

Gholshapur railway colony Behala, Kolkata Pin-700034, West Bengal,India

Current Address

PMR Residency, Bommanhalli, Bengaluru, Karnataka,India

Mobile

+91-7980029914

Email

das5simply@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/simply-das-536742136/

Skills

Design Thinking
User Experience Design
User Interface Design
Human Computer Interaction
Conceptual Design

Master Plan
Interior Design
Landscape Architecture

Building Information Modelling

Sustainable Architecture Architecture

SIMPLY DAS

REGISTERED ARCHITECT COUNCIL OF ARCHITECTURE

License	Tools
Council of Architecture - India	10010
Council of Architecture - India	Autodesk Autocad 2d
	Autodesk Revit Architecture
	Adobe Photoshop CC
Salastad Professional & Academia Experience	Google Sketchup
Selected Professional & Academic Experience	Vray
Arch Starwood, Chinar Park, Kolkata	Lumion 3d
	Microsoft Office
Gitanjali Kolkata	Rhino+ Grasshopper
Swarnamani Kolkata	Killio Grassnopper
5th Avenue, Mahishbathan, Kolkata	
Jui Avenue, Mainshbaulan, Koikata	Workshops
Laxmi Aquascape, Foreshore Road, Kolkata	vvorksnops
	Workshop On Form, Space & Order
DNC CHITS, Sri Vijaya Vidhyalaya-Metric School, Thiruvannamalai	
Undergraduate Thesis:	Seminar On Heritage Conservation
Ecotourism Resort	- Ar. Karan Grover
	Seminar On Apartment Complexes -Ar. Prassana Desai
	Seminar On Complete Design
	-Ar. Hafeez Contractor
	Seminar On Earthquake Resistance
	Building
	-Civiler. Charles Andrew
	Seminar ON Sustainability &
	Sensitizing
	-Ms. Sangeeta Kapoor,
	Sir Lawrence,
	Ar. Kalyan Chakraborty
	Seminar On Green Building
	- Ar. Charanjit Shah
	CGBMT Bangalore (Natural Building Materials and
	(Natural Building Materials and Technologies)
	Shells Architectural Form Makers
	-Dr. Sigid Adriaenenssens,
	Princeton University
	·